<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Application</string>
    <string name="review">Bheeshma Parvam Story: Micheal helms his influential family in Kochi, inspiring fear and respect through his unnerving past. When a few younger members in the household feel his power over their lives too are aggravating, they join hands with foes to clamp down on him. And the story follows what’s in store for them.
Bheeshma Parvam Review: Before Bheeshma Parvam’s release, many in its team had hinted the film is the story of families, and it has elements from Mahabharatha, The Godfather and more for the audience to look forward to.
        What you get at the theatres is an entertaining story with elements borrowed from them all, well put together to appeal to the new age audience, spiced up with some racy music.
From those who have tons of reasons to fear him to others who love him for what he has done for the family, Micheal’s (Mammootty) household is filled with members of many personality shades. And just as it is under his roof, his fearsome past and influence have earned him ample antagonists outside too. At one point a few of them join hands to bring him down and live life as they please. How much does their plan succeed?
Right from the beginning, the film is careful enough to set its pace balanced and engaging, even as it organically establishes the characters, along with their backgrounds, place in the family tree and more with ease. Mammootty pleases as the invincible hero through his towering presence, body language, punch dialogues, stunts and more, giving those seeking entertainment enough moments to feel enthralled. Shine Tom Chacko, Sudev Nair and Soubin too are in top form in their respective roles. The treatment of the story has ensured that the women characters in it respectfully portrayed and a special attention to be politically correct, rightly so, is evident and laudable. Anend C Chandran’s lens has captured the visuals with gusto and the stunt choreography was also riveting for a movie of the genre.
Sushin Shyam’s music deserves a special mention for how it elevates the feel of the proceedings, though there are a few points in which the dialogues drown in their thumping impact.
        Watching Nedumudi Venu and KPAC Lalitha on screen, probably playing the kind of characters we haven’t seen them doing much, can trigger nostalgia in many.
The film would be an entertaining outing for Mammootty fans and others looking for some déjà vu-worthy action drama story</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">MapsActivity</string>
</resources>